Excuse me, sir. Quick question for
you, man. Is this your jet?
Yeah, of course it's my jet.
And what do you do for a living to be
able to afford a private jet out here in Miami, Florida?
I had two tech companies that
I ran for like 10 years.
Yeah.
And then I sold both.
How much did you sell the companies for?
Eight figures.
Have you ever been broke before?
You know that I came to the States when I was
20 years old, almost 17 years ago, with $78 in cash.
How much money are you making a year now?
It's about $2 million annually.
Is this your Lamborghini?
Absolutely.
And what do you do for a living to be
able to afford a Lamborghini out here in Miami, Florida?
I mean, I'm an entrepreneur.
I own a few different companies, but
my main company is a marketing agency.
Over these last two years, what's been the most amount
of money that you've ever made in a single year?
Oh, man, multiple millions.
Like seven figures?
Easily, yeah.
Eight figures?
Yes.
We did $5.5 million, but $2.4 million
net, which is what I truly cared about.
We did $752 million.
How can somebody own a private jet in today's world?
First of all...
Welcome to Miami, Florida.
This city is home to nearly 40,000 millionaires.
And today, we're going to
be going all over the city,
asking these motherfuckers,
multimillionaires from seven to
eight and even nine-figure entrepreneurs,
how they became wealthy and how you can
start your path to becoming financially free in 2024.
And with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Have you ever been broke before?
As a joke.
Broke?
Are you kidding me?
This guy right here, I slept in
my car at one point in my life.
No, he didn't have money at all.
I mean, literally.
It was just that nasty.
I came from a very humble beginning
as a kid growing up in Africa.
That past day when I was seven years
old, three meals a day was a struggle.
Holes in my shoes as a kid.
I remember like yesterday.
Broke as hell.
But what I want to tell you is this.
Being broke is a temporary condition.
It really is.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Lord have mercy.
Close to two million.
Two million dollars?
Yes.
Are you a buyer or a seller?
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
That's a good one.
I sell all day.
So, okay, watch this.
Are you ready?
There are two types of people against society.
Consumers.
And what?
Producers.
Consumer consume.
Producers produce.
Who makes the most money?
Producers.
The producers.
You follow me so far on this?
Three things.
My mentor tells me this and it stays.
Number one, fall in love with people.
Number two, fall in love with sales.
Number three, fall in love with numbers.
You do those three things, nobody's going to recognize.
You're going to go back and watch this
tape a few years from now like, damn.
What's the best advice that you
would tell the younger generation today?
Make speed work to your favor.
Because you're young, but you're not forever young.
You don't procrastinate anymore.
Because procrastination.
Is the assassination of all destination.
You do not procrastinate.
And we're just talking about how
there are two types of people, right?
Givers and takers, right?
Life take from takers and give to givers.
And keep very accurate accounting.
You can't cheat it.
Give them one last deep quote
to really stick with them going forward.
This one stays with me forever and ever and ever.
Work like it's up to you
and pray like it's up to God.
That's my best quote ever.
In other words, go to work
with every fiber of your being.
Every soul.
Every part of you.
Your body.
Go all day.
But then you're only one person.
Then you have to pray to God, your
creator, to make all your dreams become a reality.
So work like it's up to you
and pray like it's up to God.
Thomas, that was phenomenal.
Question for you, sir.
I started a channel in Austin, Texas
that I grew to over three million followers.
I go all over the country just asking people a
few quick questions on their best advice to the younger generation.
Could I ask you just a
few quick questions for the channel?
Is that cool?
Go ahead.
Okay.
I guess like what industry did
you decide to pursue a career in?
You know what?
I grew up in the tech business.
Yeah.
In the tech business.
And how long have you been in tech for?
I had two tech companies that
I ran for like 10 years.
Yeah.
And then I sold both.
And now I'm enjoying life in Miami.
How much did you sell the companies for?
A fair amount.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Did you say like eight figures?
Eight figures.
Could you park?
Could we ask you a
couple questions outside of the car?
Is that cool?
Yeah.
Okay, perfect.
Thank you.
How can somebody break into the tech industry in 2024?
You know, tech business is tough.
You got to always innovate and you got to
be one step and everything is about speed to
market because when you come up with an
idea, tomorrow somebody else will come up with an
idea and you got to come up with it.
So you got to go fast.
And how long have you been an entrepreneur for?
All my life.
All your life.
What's the greatest lesson about entrepreneurship you
learned that you pass on to someone about
to start their first business in 2024?
Great people.
You got to have great people.
Yeah.
Everything, every business surrounds great people,
people that are smart, people that
are committed, people that want to be in
startups because you really dedicate your life to it.
Right.
It's 24-7.
Have you ever been broke before?
You know what?
Every entrepreneur reaches that point.
So I wouldn't say broke, but financially challenged, yes.
Yeah.
What's the best financial advice that
you ever received from a mentor?
If there's a lesson about money that
somebody taught you, what would that advice be?
Be well capitalized.
In tech, you got to have funding.
So have good partners, have smart money.
Smart money always goes a
long ways than just normal money.
What is the best industry
people should get into in 2024?
Best industry?
Tech.
AI.
The world is changing with AI software.
And if you have the knowledge, that
is the space to be in right now.
Thank you so much for your time.
So I really appreciate that.
Have a great day, sir.
Thank you.
So we were just walking around Miami Beach
and I caught my guy driving around in the
Ferrari.
You know I had to stop him for some game.
And it turns out.
He sold two tech companies for multiple eight figures.
And he just dropped some serious game.
How you can break into the tech industry in 2024.
But I love what he said.
The most important thing that helped
him throughout his career was people.
At the end of the day, if
you want to go fast, go by yourself.
But if you want to
go further, go with people together.
Great interview.
Let's go get this next one.
Have you ever been broke before?
You know that I came to the States when
I was 20 years old, almost 17 years ago, with
$78 in cash.
And I didn't speak any English.
It's very empowering.
And I'm proud of what I've done.
And looking back, I would do
it all over again, thousand times.
So you came here with $78.
Yes.
How much money are you making a year now?
It's about $2 million annually.
Where are you from?
I'm from Russia.
What's your favorite part about being
a business owner in the United States?
Freedom.
That's what I work for.
I never really cared about a month
of money, to be honest with you.
And that's not what I'm here for.
I grew up pretty poor.
So it's, you know, I just don't
want that for my children and myself.
Among yourself and the most successful people
that you know, what's that one trait that
they all have in common?
They don't complain.
They always.
On top of solution.
What is the solution?
What is it that I can do better?
So they don't sit there in self-pity and cry.
That's the one thing that I notice
about people that are very, very successful.
Entitlement is what's going to kill
you at the end, by the way.
Nobody's coming to save you, that's for sure.
How old are you now?
I'm 36.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
About six years ago was my first million.
If you were to go back and have
a conversation with your 20-year-old self, what's that advice
that you'd give to your younger self?
Don't listen to people that
don't have things that you want.
Ignore the noise.
When I was 24, everybody and
their mother told me, what lashes?
What is lashes?
Don't do it.
You know, it was crazy to a lot of people.
I just got kind of obsessed
with getting better in what I do.
I really wanted to be the
best lash artist that there is.
It was like a sick thing I
would wake up with every single day.
And even though it seems crazy
to everybody else, it's going to work.
Her story was amazing, you guys.
She moved to the United States over
15 years ago with only $78 in her.
Bank account.
She turned that into a business that's
now doing $2 million every single year.
But my favorite part about that interview was
when I asked what the most successful people
have in common.
And she said that it's that they don't
complain or feel entitled to the success that they
ultimately achieve.
At the end of the day, what you want
out of life is dependent on the work that you're
willing to put in.
So take notes from that interview and apply it.
But with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
All right, you guys, my guy just put up
in a Lamborghini years out here in Miami, Florida.
I'm going to go up and see what he was
able to do to be able to afford a Lamborghini.
Let's see what he has to say.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your Lamborghini?
Absolutely.
And what do you do for a living to
be able to afford a Lamborghini out here in Miami,
Florida?
I mean, I'm an entrepreneur.
I own a few different companies, but my
main company is a marketing agency, which kind
of feeds all of the other
companies like an ecosystem that I have.
Yeah.
And I guess like how long
have you been a business owner for?
22 months.
Exactly.
Yeah.
This month.
There's about two years.
Yeah.
Two years.
Over these last two years, what's been the
most amount of money that you've ever made
in a single year?
Last year was my first full year.
We did 5.5 million between all of the companies,
but 2.4 million net, which is what I truly
cared about.
And this year we're trying to absolutely double that.
That's incredible, man.
Have you ever been broke before?
I've been broke a few times, man.
I had a clothing store and a barbershop when
I was 18 with a business partner of mine.
He was selling drugs, went into depression,
lost my clothing store, lost my barbershop,
had to start over selling phones
out of a kiosk for Sprint.
Started investing in real estate, bought
the nicest houses in the nicest neighborhoods,
made them look the best, lost
a lot of money in real estate.
So then I had to start all over and
that's ended up what got me into insurance because
I figured out that it
was an unlimited earning potential vehicle.
As a multiple seven figure entrepreneur, what's
been the best financial advice that you ever
received?
Throughout your lifetime?
Best advice I got was from a billionaire and
I wasn't even able to get a conversation with
him until I started putting up some real numbers
and I was on his private jet and he looked
at me, he said, Eric, you know,
I've heard a lot about your life.
You got a sad story and now people
care about it because you actually have success.
But what you need to understand is anything
and everything that happens to you might not
be your fault, but it is your problem.
And eventually you have to solve that problem
or you're going to continue being broke the
rest of your life.
So as soon as you understand that it
is your responsibility and you have a mirror every
day, you look at when you get
up in the morning, you're brushing your teeth.
That's your accountability mirror.
You need to speak to yourself.
You need to speak life into
yourself because your belief system also matters.
If you don't believe you're going to be
worth eight figures, you're never going to touch
eight figures.
If you were to go back two years
ago when you were first starting your business, what's
the number one thing that you would have told yourself?
Stop fucking listening to everybody else, man.
I, you know, I started getting everybody's opinion
on what I should do, how I should
build my business, but nobody had a dream
as big as mine and nobody was truly trying
to create what I was creating.
So I started listening to my gut, man.
Gut intelligence is so important, guys.
If you do not listen to your gut
and you start listening to everybody's opinions, you're
going to end up like everybody.
So I promise you, please listen to your own gut.
And what's the best way to get that?
What's the most common mistake that people
make that keeps them broken in today's world?
Money management and time management.
Once they're an entrepreneur, they think
they don't have to come to work.
They think, oh, 8 a.m.
No, I'm self-employed.
I'm a business owner.
I don't need to come into work at 8 a.m.
Not realizing 8 a.m. is when you
can legally start prospecting and nothing else matters.
You can be the most talented sales individual in
the world, but if you do not prospect and
you do not establish relationships, you will never
be able to use your actual talents in
terms of selling, especially as an entrepreneur.
So we just put up on my guy in
the Lamborghini years, man, and he just dropped some great
game for you guys.
He became a millionaire at 32
because his business was so good.
He just did $5 million this last year.
But what did he say?
His billionaire mentor told him, no matter
what you're going through, no matter what
problem you have, it may not be
your fault, but it is still your problem.
So it's up to you to
find a way to solve it.
Great interview, man.
Let's go get this next one.
All right, you guys, I got a
very special surprise for you right now.
We're at a $15 million
mansion out here in Miami, Florida.
We're going to go up and find out what
they were able to do to put themselves here.
Let's see what they have to say.
What's going on, Chandy?
Hey, James.
How you doing, man?
Thanks for having us out here, man.
All is well.
You know, everybody who's been dying to know, they
want to know what you do for a living
to be able to afford this place out in Miami.
I'm an orthodontist, fixed teeth.
What's been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Oh, man, multiple millions.
And it's going back into real estate and
shopping centers and kind of like growing from there.
You say like seven figures?
Easily.
Yeah.
Eight figures?
Yes.
Yeah.
Now, what is the secret
to creating wealth in real estate?
Like, there's a big misconception that you have
to have a ton of money to start creating
wealth.
But like, what's been your secret
to creating wealth in real estate?
This is how I create wealth in real estate.
I focus on my practices that grow.
That gives me the cash flow.
So I don't really need outside investors.
I can put that cash flow right
into like shopping centers and medical buildings.
And then the next year, keep on doing
the same thing as those properties get cash flow
as well.
Now, this is a $15 million spot right here.
Did you go to college?
Of course.
You went to college?
Yes.
Do you think a college degree is
necessary to be successful in today's society?
I mean, I'm old school and conservative a little bit.
But yeah, I think college, even higher learning is
going to help you get into like the bigger,
bigger stuff.
What do you mean by bigger stuff?
Your core business that you develop
yourself as a doctor or an attorney.
And now that you can grow it multiple
ways without like a lot of barriers to entry,
because it's not easy.
I went to dental school and orthodontic school.
So that was 11 years.
And a lot of people are not
going to go through 11 years of school.
What's one lesson about business that you
would give to somebody that they will not
learn in school?
I think, you know, I'm into like shopping centers now.
And the last two deals I did, I got
directly in front of the owner, the seller, and he
liked me and people want to
work with people that they like.
So I think if you can be personable and
likable, people want to do business with people they
like.
Man, I appreciate you, brother.
This Miami video has been unreal, but I
want you to comment down below who's been your
favorite interview and why.
We love connecting with you guys.
I want to know all
what you think about this video.
But with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
All right, you guys, we are currently at
a private jet airport out here in Miami, Florida.
There's some flights landing in right now.
I'm going to go up and see if we can find
a way to get in and talk to some of these
private jet owners to figure out what they were
able to do to afford a private jets out
here in Miami, Florida.
As you guys can see, signature flight support.
We got to find a way in here, man.
There's jets coming in every minute.
So we got to see what they have to say.
Come on.
All right, you guys, my guy just
landed in a private jet and he's off.
I'm going to go up and see what he was able
to do to be able to afford a private jet out
here in Miami.
Let's see what he has to say.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your jet?
Yeah, of course it's my jet.
And what do you do for a living to be
able to afford a private jet out here in Miami,
Florida?
I've been running my own business for 30 years.
Actually?
Actually.
I wouldn't lie to you.
And over these 30 years, what's the most amount
of money that you've ever made in a single
year?
Tens of millions of dollars.
I've had sales and exits of $100
million for companies I've run and exited successfully.
I go all the way.
I go all over the country just
asking business owners their advice to young entrepreneurs.
Is it cool if we ask
you a few questions for the channel?
100%, dude.
You got courage to ask questions, I will answer them.
We can go right on here if you want.
Is that cool?
Let's run it.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Out of one of your businesses, what was
the most that you've made in a single year?
Best year I've had was last year and we
did $752 million in rev for the year in 23.
As a multiple nine-figure entrepreneur, what has
been the best financial advice that you
ever received?
You know who Arthur Blank is?
Very familiar.
Okay.
I was at a meeting 14 years
ago and I was making some money.
I was making some money and trying to figure some
stuff out and he asked me if I had any
questions.
And what's weird about people
is they don't have no questions.
Dude, if you leave me in a room with
somebody doing better than me, I will ask them questions
for like literally until they have
to tell me to shut up.
So I'm asking him some questions and he's answering.
Nobody else is asking questions.
And I said, sir, if you could give me
one advice on why you're able, because at the
time we were talking about Home Depot.
Why are you able to launch Home Depot?
And it's such an amazing company.
He said, first of all, every business opportunity I
looked at, I made sure that I always fed
my business, right?
I didn't want to starve it.
He said, in Home Depot.
While I knew we were going to have very small
margins and I knew it would take a while to
make money.
Once we started making money, a little bit
of a lot of been like more than enough.
We'd had no problems.
So he started talking about that concept and
I started to learn patience from a lot of
these guys.
And then I had a guy
who's a billionaire 10, 12 times over.
And he said, take every business
opportunity, approach it like a three-legged stool.
I said, okay, what does that mean?
He said, every decision you make, any decision
you're making has to be great for your client
or your consumer.
Second, it has to be great for
your agent or your employer, independent contract, your
consultant.
Okay.
I said, what does that mean?
He said, it can't harm the company.
He said, but that'll take patience because
most people run their business where they
make every decision that's great for them.
Whatever scraps are left, but they don't tend
to be sustainable because other guys are doing
it your way.
In the life insurance deal, even though we
did that kind of rev last year, through the
first three years, I wasn't paying myself a lot.
And a lot of people get
into business to get rich right away.
I got into business to get free
and I knew eventually I'd become wealthy.
Rich, you could say you've made
400 grand a year, you're rich.
I wanted to not worry about money.
That's been the best business lesson I've
ever learned because most people get in the
business and after about 60, 90,
120 days, two years, they're frustrated.
You know, everybody used to always
say, what's the first rule of business?
Stay in business.
First couple of years.
But everybody says it's a grind until they're in it.
And then they're like, I can't buy that $400,000 car.
And it's like, okay, Tommy, welcome to the real world.
And I'm always like, dude, I don't know.
I don't, I ran my business.
I ran it.
I took business advice from people that
were in a better place than me.
But personally, anybody around me that
was talking, I wasn't listening to nothing.
I mean, if people are weighing you
down, dude, you get the anchor off.
Like if you, if you're a good swimmer, if
you can't swim and you jump in the water,
I will jump in to help you.
The minute you grab me and I think you're
bringing me down, I'm going to punch you in
the face as hard as I can.
I'm going to swim back to safety.
I'm going to pray for you.
I'm going to call 911.
And then what happened?
I'm like, I jumped in to help him
and he started trying to drown me too.
I'm out.
What's been your secret to sales?
How have you been able to consistently land
massive deals with huge clients over all these
years?
What's your secret to selling in a competitive industry?
Why do you think most people struggle with sales?
I don't think they believe in themselves.
That's hate.
That's a good answer because that's part of it.
And then that lack of belief
causes them not to work hard.
The biggest thing I want to
sell people is belief in themselves.
You give me a product, if people need it
and I believe in it, I will sell it.
I don't give a shit what it is.
It doesn't matter.
If you go sell these shoes,
I'd be like, are they good shoes?
Damn, I'll sell them.
Sell the shirt.
I'll sell that shirt off of your back to him.
You can build the belief in yourself,
but people don't want to work hard.
The greatest thing for your self-image by far is work.
That's the greatest thing.
So weirdly enough, I became really good
at sales because I called more people.
I wasn't going to take no for an answer.
I wasn't worried about being judged.
So I didn't think it was
that competitive because most people won't work.
I always tell people.
When I started making money, my friends were
like, yo, you think you're better than us?
Behind my back, obviously.
And I'd be like, I
don't think I'm better than you.
I just want more in life than you.
I'm not any better than you.
Hey, sadly enough, you can do exactly what I'm doing.
Guys, that's a wrap on today's video.
Be sure to leave a like
and subscribe for amazing content coming soon.
We're on a way to bring you guys some of the best
advice from some of the most successful business owners in the entire world.
So stay tuned for that.
Sean, where can everybody find you out?
Anywhere, man.
Instagram.
My name is Sean, S-H-A-W-N.
Mike is my last name, but it's M-E-N.
A-I-K-E.
So Instagram, YouTube, follow, like, share, please.
Because this guy is an absolute stud, man.
A lot of people do this,
but a lot of them aren't good.
Yeah.
You're really good, man.
Appreciate you.
Appreciate you, dude.
And guys, be sure to click here to watch our full video going all over Dallas asking
multimillionaires how they became wealthy and how you can start your path to becoming financially free in 2024.